{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":3816,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":14,"width":1366,"height":768,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index_scorm.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si51761","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"COURSE OBJECTIVE ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"PRACTICE USING WORK ORDERS IN THE LOCUSVIEW WEB APP ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_86","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_86","title":"Follow the green prompts and click through the simulation. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"browser_next_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"browser_next_37","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si53817","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si53844","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide7703","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si51761","Text_Caption_7","Text_Caption_86","browser_next_37","si53817","si53844"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7703"}}},{"id":"Image_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_78","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_92","title":"Click to open a Work Order. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_31","roles":{}},{"id":"Click_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_15","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide53510","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"click-open work order","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_78","Text_Caption_92","WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_31","Click_Box_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":477},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide53510"}}},{"id":"Image_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_77","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_84","title":"The Details tab provides an overview of all data collected within the Work Order.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_121","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"browser_next_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"browser_next_36","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si53322","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si53349","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide44564","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"note-details tab","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_77","Text_Caption_84","SmartShape_121","browser_next_36","si53322","si53349"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide44564"}}},{"id":"Image_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_80","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_94","title":"Web Users have the ability to edit the data within a Work Order, and to delete Work Orders.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_122","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"browser_next_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"browser_next_38","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si53989","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si54002","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide54018","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"note-edit and delete","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_80","Text_Caption_94","SmartShape_122","browser_next_38","si53989","si54002"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide54018"}}},{"id":"si52569","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":"Click the pencil icon to edit the Work Order data. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"ALERTS_OVERVIEW_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"ALERTS_OVERVIEW_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_24","roles":{}},{"id":"Click_Box_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide44359","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"click-pencil icon","thumbnail":"","children":["si52569","Text_Caption_78","ALERTS_OVERVIEW_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_24","Click_Box_8"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":165},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide44359"}}},{"id":"Image_79","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_79","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_93","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_93","title":"In the Project Budget field, type 350,000.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_2","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"browser_next_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"browser_next_40","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si55508","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si55535","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide53652","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"type-project budget","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_79","Text_Caption_93","Text_Entry_Box_2","browser_next_40","si55508","si55535"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide53652"}}},{"id":"Image_81","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_81","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_95","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_95","title":"Click “Save” to save changes to the Work Order.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_33","roles":{}},{"id":"Click_Box_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_17","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"$350,000      ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide54162","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"click-save edits","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_81","Text_Caption_95","WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_33","Click_Box_17","Text_Caption_100"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":477},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide54162"}}},{"id":"Image_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_82","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_96","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_96","title":"Click the trash can icon to delete the Work Order.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"ALERTS_OVERVIEW_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"ALERTS_OVERVIEW_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_34","roles":{}},{"id":"Click_Box_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_18","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"$350,000      ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide54263","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"click-trash icon","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_82","Text_Caption_96","ALERTS_OVERVIEW_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_34","Click_Box_18","Text_Caption_101"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":165},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide54263"}}},{"id":"Image_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_83","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_97","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_97","title":"Note, a warning message prompts the User to confirm. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"browser_next_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"browser_next_39","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si54394","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si54407","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide54423","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"note-edit and delete","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_83","Text_Caption_97","browser_next_39","si54394","si54407"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide54423"}}},{"id":"Image_84","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_84","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_98","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","title":"Click “Delete” to confirm changes. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_35","roles":{}},{"id":"Click_Box_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_19","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide54530","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"click-delete","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_84","Text_Caption_98","WORK_ORDER_HIGHLIGHT_BOX_35","Click_Box_19"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":477},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide54530"}}},{"id":"si51862","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26692q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26722","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26729","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A Work Order can be accessed and updated by both Web Users and  Field Workers in real time. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26744","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26748","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26744_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26755","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26759","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26755_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26776","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26692q0","for":"Slide26692q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26793","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26692q0","for":"Slide26692q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26806","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26692q0","for":"Slide26692q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26849","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26692q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26862","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26692q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26692","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si51862","si26722","si26729","si26748","si26759","si26776","si26793","si26806"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":450},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26692"},"question":{"interactionId":"26709","quizId":379,"title":"True/False","text":"A Work Order can be accessed and updated by both Web Users and \rField Workers in real time.\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"]}}},{"id":"si51844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide25087q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25117","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25124","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A Work Order is a container of project-related data, including... ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25139","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25143","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Assets ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25139_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Assets\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25150","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25154","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Job location and schedule ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25150_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Job location and schedule\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25952","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Forms ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25948_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Forms\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25963","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25967","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the Above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25963_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the Above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25171","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25087q1","for":"Slide25087q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25188","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25087q1","for":"Slide25087q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25201","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25087q1","for":"Slide25087q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide25087q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25995","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect. Try again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide25087q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32322","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect. Try again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide25087q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32335","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect. Try again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide25087q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25087","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Q1 MC","thumbnail":"","children":["si51844","si25117","si25124","si25143","si25154","si25952","si25967","si25171","si25188","si25201"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":450},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25087"},"question":{"interactionId":"25104","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"A Work Order is a container of project-related data, including...\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"]}}},{"id":"si51853","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26374q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26152","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":"Fill-In-The-Blank ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26164","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"A Locusview Work Order___________ manual data entry of paper-based data gathered in the field.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"replaces ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26175_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"5","roles":{"answer":{"title":"replaces\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"relies on ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26186_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"7","roles":{"answer":{"title":"relies on\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26280","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26374q2","for":"Slide26374q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26292","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26374q2","for":"Slide26374q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26304","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"SUBMIT ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26374q2","for":"Slide26374q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26335","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26374q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_6","title":"Incorrect. Try again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide26374q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26374","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Q2 MC","thumbnail":"","children":["si51853","si26152","si26164","si26179","si26190","si26280","si26292","si26304"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":450},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26374"},"question":{"interactionId":"26108","quizId":379,"title":"Fill-In-The-Blank\r","text":"A Locusview Work Order___________ manual data entry of paper-based data gathered in the field.\r\r","ikc":true,"type":"knowledgeCheck","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"]}}},{"id":"si51896","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"WELL DONE! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si51914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"THIS CONCLUDES THE LESSON CLOSE THIS WINDOW TO CONTINUE ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26916","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si51896","si51914"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":225},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26916"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"WRA-103 WORK ORDERS_SIMULATION","class":"project","title":"WRA-103 WORK ORDERS_SIMULATION","children":["Slide7703","Slide53510","Slide44564","Slide54018","Slide44359","Slide53652","Slide54162","Slide54263","Slide54423","Slide54530","Slide26692","Slide25087","Slide26374","Slide26916"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide26692q0","Slide25087q1","Slide26374q2"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide7703","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide53510","title":"click-open work order"},{"id":"Slide44564","title":"note-details tab"},{"id":"Slide54018","title":"note-edit and delete"},{"id":"Slide44359","title":"click-pencil icon"},{"id":"Slide53652","title":"type-project budget"},{"id":"Slide54162","title":"click-save edits"},{"id":"Slide54263","title":"click-trash icon"},{"id":"Slide54423","title":"note-edit and delete"},{"id":"Slide54530","title":"click-delete"},{"id":"Slide26692","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide25087","title":"Q1 MC"},{"id":"Slide26374","title":"Q2 MC"},{"id":"Slide26916","title":"Slide 14"}]}